{  "questions"  : [ {
    
      "question":" 1 .Which of the following is true about ng-bind directive?",
     
      "options":
        [
          "ng-bind directive binds the AngularJS Application data to HTML tags ",
          "ng-bind updates the model created by ng-model directive to be displayed in the html tag ",
          "ng-bind updates html control data when controller changes the model",
          "All of the above."     
        ],
        "answer": 4
        
     },
    {
    "question": "2.Which of the following directive bootstraps AngularJS framework? .",
     "options":
      [ "ng-init",
        "ng-app",
        "ng-controller",
        "ng-bootstrap"
        ],
        "answer": 4
    
    },
    {
      "question": "3.  How angular.module works?.",
       "options":
        [
          "angular.module is used to create AngularJS modules along with its dependent modules ",
           "angular.module is primarily used to create application module",
           " Both of the above.",
            "None of the above."
          ],
          "answer": 3
      
      },
      {
        "question": "4. Which components can be injected as a dependency in AngularJS.",
        "options":
         [
           " Application Module", 
           " constant",
            " value" ,
            " factory"
           ],
           "answer": 4
        
        },
        {
          "question": "5. Which of the following is true about ng-include directive?",
          "options":
           [
             " Embed HTML pages within a HTML page using ng-include directive",
               "Embed JS files within a HTML page using ng-include directive",
             " Both of the above.",
             " None of the above."
             ],
             "answer": 1
          },
          {
            "question": "6.Which of the following is a valid AngularJS expression?",
             "options":
              [
                 "{{ 2 + 2 }}",
                 "{ 2 + 2 }",
                 "(( 2 + 2 ))",
                 "{ (2 + 2) }"
               ],
                "answer": 1 
            
            },
          {
            "question": "7. What is $scope?",
            "options":
             [
               "It transfers data between a controller and view ",
                "It transfers data between model and controller",
                " It is a global scope in AngularJS",
                 "None of the above"
               ],
               "answer": 2
           
           },
           {
            "question": "8. AngularJS directives can be written in HTML element as:.",
            "options":
             [
                 " Tag",
                 " Attribute",
                 "Class name",
                 "All of the above"
               ],
               "answer": 4
           
           },
           
           {
            "question": "9. The ng-model directive is used for __________.",
            "options":
             [
                " One-way data binding",
                 "Two-way data binding",
                 "Binding view to controller",
                 "None of the above"
               ],
               "answer": 2
           
           },
           {
            "question": "10. Which of the following statements are true?",
            "options":
             [
                 "Expression cannot contain condition, loop or RegEx",
                 "Expression cannot declare a function",
                 "Expression cannot contain comma, void or return keyword",
                 "All of the above"
               ],
               "answer": 1
           
           }
           
      ]}
     